Now, let's look at how to compute the confidence interval for our sample.
现在让我们来看看如何计算样本的置信区间
We've already found the center of the interval,
我们已经找到了区间的中心
that is a probability of a click.
点击的概率
The equation was p hat, or the estimated probability equals X over N,
方程是 p? 或者说预计概率 等于 X 除以 N
where X was the number of users who clicked and
这里 X 是指点击的用户数量
N was the total number of users who visited the page.
N 是访问页面的用户总数量
In this example, p hat is 100 over 1000, or 0.1.
在这里 p? 是 100 除以 1000 或者说0.1
So, the center of the confidence interval will be 0.1.
所以置信区间的中心应为 0.1
Next, I want to calculate the width of the confidence interval,
然后我想计算置信区间的宽度
which is also called the margin of error, or m.
也称为误差幅度 或者简称为 m
To do this,
为此
I'll need to use the standard error of the binomial distribution.
我需要使用二项发布的标准误差
Recall that if the sample is large enough,
之前有提过 如果样本规模够大
instead of using the binomial distribution,
可以不使用二项发布
I can assume the distribution is normal, like this blue line.
我假设分布是正态的 如蓝线所示
A good rule of thumb is that if N times p hat is greater than 5,
这里有个好的经验原则 如果 N 乘以 p? 大于5
it's safe to assume a normal distribution.
则可以把它假设为正态分布
You should also check that N times 1 minus p hat, is greater than 5.
你还应检查 N 乘以 1 减去 p? 应大于5
But, for small click-through probabilities like we usually see,
但是 像我们平时缩减的较小的点击概率
this is the more stringent condition.
这个条件太苛刻了
In our case, N times p hat is 100, so the assumption should be safe here.
在这里 N 乘以 p? 是 100 所以这样猜想也是合理的
When we can use the normal approximation, then the width of
如果我们可以采用正态近似 置信区间的宽度
the confidence interval, that is the margin of error, will be equal
即误差幅度 等于 z 置信度
to the z-score of the confidence level, times the standard error.
乘以标准误差
And for the binomial distribution,
而在二项发布中
the standard error's the square root of p hat times 1 minus p hat over N.
标准误差等于 p? 乘以 1 减 p 除以 N 的平方根
If you look at this formula, you'll notice a few things.
如果你观察这个公式 你会发现一些内容
The amount of random variation we expect in our sample,
我们预计样本中的随机变化量
the width of the confidence interval,
置信区间的宽度
is a function of both the proportion of successes and the size of the sample.
是样本中成功的比例以及样本规模的函数
This means we need to consider the proportion of successes when we decide
也就是说我们在决定采集多少样本时 需要考虑成功的比例
how many samples to collect, which we'll talk about again later this lesson.
本课稍后会谈到这个内容
When the success probability is farther from 0.5 then
成功概率离 0.5 越远
the standard error will be smaller, which means the distribution is tighter,
标准误差会越小 也就意味着分布更加紧凑
which means the confidence interval will be smaller.
也就是置信区间更小
Similarly, if the number of samples is larger, the standard error and
相似的 如果样本数量越大
the confidence interval will also be smaller.
标准误差与置信区间则越小
Now I'll need to find the z-score for
现在我需要寻求 95% 置信区间
the boundary of a 95% confidence interval.
边界的 z 值
For a normal distribution with a mean of 0 and a standard deviation of 1,
而均值为 0 标准偏差为 1 的正态分布
which is also called a z distribution.
也称为 Z 分布
With 95% confidence, the true value would be within 1.96 and
95% 的置信度下 真正的值应该在
negative 1.96 of the estimate we observed.
预计值的 1.9 6与 -1.96 之间
The value 1.96 is called a z-score, and
1.96 这个值称为 z 分数
you can look it up in a table like the one linked in the instructor's notes.
我们可以在表格中查询这个数字 如讲师注释中的链接所示
In this case, since we're doing a two-tailed test,
这里 因为我们进行的是双尾检验
each tail will contain 2.5% of the distribution.
每一个尾部包含分布的 2.5%
So 1.96 is the z-score for 97.5%, or 100 minus 2.5.
所以 1.96 是 97.5% 的 Z 分数 或 100 减去 2.5
In our case, the margin of error comes out to about 0.019.
在我们的例子中 得到的误差幅度大约是 0.019
So, we'll add this margin of error to the point estimate to get the upper
我们将此误差幅度与中心点预估值相加
bound of 0.119, and subtract to get the lower bound of 0.081.
得到上限 0.119 然后相减 得到下限 0.081
This means, if you'd run the experiment again with another thousand page views,
也就是说 你继续对几千次页面访问进行实验
you'd maybe expect to see between 80 and 120 clicks, but more or
你可以预估 每一千次访问中点击在 80 至 120 次之间
less than that would be pretty surprising.
超过或低于这个值都是让人吃惊的数字
Now, let's say you made a similar measurement on a different page,
加入你对不同的页面进行了相似的测量
and this time you got 2000 total users and 300 of them clicked.
现在你得到总共 2000 名用户 其中 300 位点击了按钮
And let's say, you wanted a 99% confidence level.
然后假如 你想要一个 99% 的置信度
Calculate the upper and lower bounds of the confidence interval, and
计算置信区间的上限和下限
write the numbers in these boxes to three decimal places.
在方框内写入数字 精确至小数点后三位
To do this, you'll need a z-score table, and
为此 你需要一个 z 分数表
you can find a link to one in the instructor's notes.
你可以在讲师注释中找到一个链接
Again, you should use a two-tailed test.
再次说明 你需要使用双尾检验